[
  {
    "question": "The ovule is a small structure attached to the placenta by means of a stalk called ______.",
    "answer": "funicle"
  },
  {
    "question": "The body of the ovule fuses with funicle in the region called ______.",
    "answer": "hilum"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hilum represents the junction between ______ and funicle.",
    "answer": "ovule"
  },
  {
    "question": "Each ovule has one or two protective envelopes called ______.",
    "answer": "integuments"
  },
  {
    "question": "Integuments encircle the nucellus except at the tip where a small opening called the ______ is organised.",
    "answer": "micropyle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Opposite the micropylar end is the ______, representing the basal part of the ovule.",
    "answer": "chalaza"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enclosed within the integuments is a mass of cells called the ______.",
    "answer": "nucellus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cells of the nucellus have abundant reserve ______ materials.",
    "answer": "food"
  },
  {
    "question": "Located in the nucellus is the embryo sac or ______ gametophyte.",
    "answer": "female"
  },
  {
    "question": "An ovule generally has a single embryo sac formed from a ______.",
    "answer": "megaspore"
  }
]











